Oh an update is available should I
update later later yeah
all right guys hold the skull piece yeah
how NASA's suck huh no not that I don't
want that oh you've tied of that cable
nice okay yeah we're about to see the
the first Aeon summer yeah Oh
intelligence I don't know we tested this
Oh add I added that no regret no
regression no regressions that's right
all right so we are on our way to Colma
Cadillac
um I just called them up Oh was that
line yeah there's there's some you know
triangles I think the path is maybe
being clipped in an odd way being
clipped cuz the thing but like
we're gonna do better than that yeah why
really says tonight just it about okay
will Sweden oh cool um so yeah guys no
all right a Cadillac I called them up I
was like yo you got any super cruise I
could test drive and they were like we
have one so look at me do I look like
someone who would buy a Cadillac should
we go back and get changed
talk talk talk about how Cadillacs have
been in your family for 200 years
grandpa's Cadillac grandpa had a
Cadillac that's true yeah that's true he
swears by them that's the MPC girl that
is nice it's the new 7up line seven
uploading make seven of yours
let's forget yeah we're so where's the
where's Cadillac dealership
I'm fired we have to go another few
minutes nice like Daly City next
okoma where there are more dead than
living yes
due to the the graveyards oh I like this
mall compiling this is beautiful
interface
I think yeah I think we'll just smooth
that out it's gonna be a super Cruz
versus own pilots cup so we'll go into
the dealership how odd is it if we ask
to periscope our test drive I think I
don't think it's that odd you know today
today everyone everyone knows that if
they can use the internet as a marketing
vehicle so I think this dealership would
be very happy to have their their
products you know shown shown on the
Internet so if we just say we're
vlogging you know make sure we lock down
the chest right we're vloggers we talk
about car yeah yeah we're car bloggers
just a vlog yeah there's no like
competition here there's no like it's no
nothing bad I'm just talking about
whether we like super cruise or not yeah
certainly
I really we really might buy the car
well you're really my yeah I'm not just
saying that's go please do you believe
me yeah I believe we we can but we can
buy this car you know how popular is the
CTS honestly I they're more super cruise
users or open pilot users it's close
that's like seriously I've been sold
like cockpits no way yeah oh there
really might be more open
oh I guess so good I mean there's this
this dealership at a major city has only
got one so there really might be ya know
like they sell no it's even worse than
that they I think they sell like I think
they sold like 300 of that car last year
and then how many of those have the
option package I literally think there's
more cars on autopilot to press this is
this is true hey I mean just wait until
all these Hondas and Toyotas are
outfitted well we're gonna we're gonna
beat you but the Bay Bridge is gonna be
littered with eons yeah
yawn convoy locally on club you know
start start your local young club get
your commuter convoy for a hyper
efficient commute
I love that our steam turns below
oh yeah the civic the civic is an
incredible drive around town even answer
some questions its 4G everywhere in the
bay pretty much there's some there's a
t-mobile dead zone on the Bay Bridge
so my music always cuts out on my
commute but other than that yeah 4G
coverage is very good in the Bay Area
altameyer should be better about caching
like two songs forward I don't know why
they don't do that yeah at least have an
option you know use more of my data yeah
I have unlimited data please cache more
things I vanilla gorilla is this the new
model we can't climate or no no this is
the this is this is the old model with
HDR guys but it performs much better in
difficult lighting conditions to the new
HDR yeah I think the thing people are
blaming on HDR was actually the blame of
the autofocus and it seems like it only
affects a certain percentage of adults
are using the pedal in this car no this
is the Civic so it has built-in
stop-and-go so no need for the no need
for the pedal
but yeah no I think the I think what a
lot of people complained about I had a
lot more to do with autofocus and it
only affected a small percent I haven't
seen you said there's a little bit
where's with HDR sometimes I really I
agree with you I don't think it's any
worse with HDR I think it's only the
autofocus was the main source of you
know uncertainty on the lands fixing
tell me tonight guys
yep open release to develop we're never
doing anymore to release people just
complain open those forever develop I'll
ever develop it'll be in beta for eight
years like Gmail like Jim yeah except
there's no invites for open palette you
know it's just the barrier entry is can
you can you install this and you plug he
mounts an e one can you plug in defend
and the giraffe here under to the other
we should upgrade our antenna yeah the
cross is totally visible you don't need
the distance to the car like I felt
confident looking at that cross that it
had the car
yeah certainly yeah the system I think
you've kind of said he made some fix to
the NPC as well foot lengths right yeah
he did improve the one lane one way
invisible we've been coming up with some
theories as I've been working on as
we're working on new models and like new
measure risers that it just works way
better in the Civic than other cars
because you know the Civic has a
different like when you're going around
a turn in a car it doesn't turn around
the eel it turns around some point at
the back of that car and that point is
speed and car dependent to do so we have
to make sure we can canonicalize our
models for that which you know if
everyone's drive around this this model
was all trained all Civic data right so
we do yeah we do have a lot of cars
start we're understanding them more and
more all the time
are we building HD maps yet yes yes we
are not quite releasing them because it
takes a lot of work to build and we're
being really strict with ourselves
but by the end of the year yeah you will
see you will see HD maps from come out
in the open
you have wheelbase and such data head
yeah we have we can certainly get
wheelbase data yeah that's all all
public when we plan on releasing them by
the end of the year see the maps about
what a wheelbase will be on the maps
wise flexor a harder than can assume
that this GM dealership is the same
thing as the Cadillac dealership let's
try to use the Honda navigation system
to navigate us to the calculation Wow
first bad search enter search
[Music]
lack what are the odds this is going to
work
I'm Stuart Cadillac okay let's navigate
sorry about the video quality guys this
is t-mobile's network auntie's att's
network but why am i arriving in
kilometres this is symmetric Pacific
symmetric tonight can I tell it not to
be a metric Civic that Ian's unit units
anybody choose parsecs
oh good no miles oh now I know I tell
them all that over
I'm not gonna work on left driving cars
too bad yeah we got a Vette that little
clip of that triangle yeah yeah that's
settlements not the pretty quick
Oh
[Music]
the alert covers
there was a path yeah yeah
I felt
you want to hide the path or go past the
passport
no the alert just covers it is all I'm
saying like
yeah
guys this is the this is the existing
model stop the new my eyes your to
understand the new model was actually
not efficient right some people got it
that's impossible to do a vision I'm
looking like well beyond where the car
could reasonably say with that with that
model I mean it is a model today yeah in
the future the mock the model and the
map will be working together at least
well yeah let's talk about super cruise
works super cruise is pretty much all
about there's no real model in super
cruise except to avoid dynamic stuff it
has five radars for on the corners and
then one phone case of radar and they're
all connected on flex right it has a
forward facing camera which I think what
it does with the forward facing camera
is to text the lane lines and then it
uses dead reckoning and a map to kind of
merge that all together
I think if there are math bugs just
disengages like if the camera and a map
don't agree the officer on the mountain
we shouldn't show that if we know what's
gonna make the turn
I think I think what we should do is
currently it has a fixed the the steer
control alert has a fixed time and so we
don't we don't just turn it off when we
know you're you're you're in the clear
assume you can just will be more
aggressive about we want to be tabled by
flickering we don't want to flicker this
is true
[Music]
George is it time to do haircut me yeah
it's time for me to go do I look like I
will buy a Cadillac no I don't think I
do I think they might give too much hair
yeah Andy's in the car Andy and George
and Andy on you know honestly I went if
the carpool lane says I need three
people to drive and I only have two
I consider the EON to be intelligent
life so if I ever get pulled over in the
carpool lane for that you know I'm
promoting the future right here I had
that Yeun really mounted like right in
the middle he's like you can't you got
off though because you know you
convinced and working on safety systems
drivers wait why didn't you tell me I
even put it in the nav system full
screen is shipping to develop tonight I
put in the nav system
I like that backup
oh yeah the backup camera is really good
some people are just really tied to
their own stuff I can see on an app
sucks by Toyota honestly we should
really just be using Waze
you've got about 2,000 miles of HD maps
of look nice keep giving us the data all
the data you provide especially dated
with a great panda is fundamental to the
future of Khmer I we have told them that
I yeah you need a great panda top in
order to be part of the HDFS we can't
make a at least for now we can't make a
map precise enough that's why we made
the great panda so that we can get high
enough precision GPS yeah that we do
appreciate all of your data yeah like a
telephone still no lead car distance in
UI that's not we don't think it's coming
back if you want it you can absolutely
make that change I've seen there's some
some Forks that have already already
done that but I don't think we'll get
we're gonna be up streaming that what is
important is for us to show you that it
does detect a lead car and that's what
we have the Red Cross for yeah so we may
change the UI with the Red Cross if it
is any at any point not not clear but
it's an MPC reset right
all right nice nice San Francisco view
right here
make the Red Cross bigger yes perhaps
maybe a little bit of a glow to it
yeah if it's on a red car that's true
yeah I also heard people saying that
looks too much like brake lights it's
kind of true I think we can do better I
really like that path being cut by the
car
man that looks a lame OS - no it looks
like we like know things BAM it's fast
well I considers the car to be there for
a little longer than
driving at night in Idaho the red cross
blends in to brake lights so yeah yeah
certainly we we'd like we'd like to have
a distance independent indicator that
that works so we'll certainly keep will
certainly test any future UI change on
on brake lights at night and on red cars
and make sure that it uh it's tap how
come it's not swipe not implemented
swipes not implement wicked we can
implement yeah I mean that would that's
the natural motion for me yeah I would
like that to work if possible when our
great panda tools come in crop load to
see the position of the satellites
likely I want to say we then put in
three weeks perhaps we'll have you'll
have you'll have the ability to view the
satellites on your yawn in the great
Panda so we're also doing a big open
source release around the great Dan dodo
you know that like huh like like the
camera company okay it's nothing else
okay all right I probably know what it
is I just don't know what the code yeah
I know that's yeah that's what we're
gonna call it tip like like like like
like like the dead dogs but I saw a lot
you know I saw like it sound like that
yeah so you know great fan of people
will be very happy
the great pandas really like for its
price it's the most precise GPS you can
buy
what about Schiffer on phone using
Galileo first great panda it doesn't
matter which constellation use it right
it's on the phone this matter if using
like glonass galileo or gps the problem
that has a lot more to do with the
antenna and the update rate um so the
update rate can be hacked so we've done
that on the eon so the EON gps is a bit
better than i've been a normal phone but
we can't do anything about the antenna
our rights to a Cadillac I've been to
his GM Malak Gary pushing get pull on a
loop was get pulling on old vanilla
gorilla that's how you stay updated you
know you never know when the updates
gonna come out so you should always be
[Music]
cool visitor parking are they gonna
notice we're not driving at GM we're
allowed to park next to all these cars
all rights go peace we got to go inside
we got to go be nice to people you know
me I'm buy a Cadillac it really might
buy one of these if I really like if we
like it yeah we're gonna test drive
first though gonna test our first
insight all right all right
well thanks
[Music]